<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Technological Magic</title>
    <link>https://doctorjax.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Technological Magic</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/DoctorJax/blog/main/hugoprofilepicture.png</url>
      <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/DoctorJax/blog/main/hugoprofilepicture.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:04:42 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://doctorjax.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Dotfiles</title>
      <link>https://doctorjax.github.io/posts/my-dotfiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:04:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doctorjax.github.io/posts/my-dotfiles/</guid>
      <description>If you want my dotfiles or you&amp;rsquo;re me and setting up a new computer, then this might be helpful.
Packages My dotfiles kinda revolve around Arch Linux, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean they don&amp;rsquo;t work on other distros. However, I&amp;rsquo;m currently only going to give a guide for Arch Linux because I&amp;rsquo;m lazy.
Paru AUR Helper sudo pacman -S --needed base-devel git clone https://aur.archlinux.org/paru.git cd paru makepkg -si Needed &amp;amp; Recommended Packages paru -S \ # Window Manager Stuff awesome awesome-freedesktop-git rofi picom python-pywal nitrogen \ # Zsh zsh zsh-syntax-highlighting zsh-autosuggestions \ # Terminal alacritty \ # Extras ranger cmus nemo neofetch pfetch lolcat nerd-fonts-complete htop \ # Text Editors vim neovim emacs libreoffice \ # Browsers brave-bin firefox \  # Rust and cargo should get installed with alacritty cargo install exa ripgrep du-dust Starship Prompt Here&amp;rsquo;s their website, but I&amp;rsquo;m going to have this command here so I can easily copy and paste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proxmox First Install</title>
      <link>https://doctorjax.github.io/posts/proxmox-first-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 21:40:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doctorjax.github.io/posts/proxmox-first-install/</guid>
      <description>Proxmox is a great Linux based hypervisor. It&amp;rsquo;s Debian based and is really easy to set up.
No-Subscription Repo While by default you need to pay for Promox to get updates, you can enable the non-subscription repo to get updates anyway. To do so, you could follow the Proxmox wiki, or just add this line to your /etc/apt/sources.list:
deb http://download.proxmox.com/debian/pve bullseye pve-no-subscription Updating When updating, do NOT just apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; apt upgrade, it will break things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Is Interesting</title>
      <link>https://doctorjax.github.io/posts/hugo-is-interesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 23:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doctorjax.github.io/posts/hugo-is-interesting/</guid>
      <description>So, I wanted a way to create a wiki/blog so that I could document all of the stuff that I do inside of my homelab, just in case I break something and need to fix it.
Why I Didn&amp;rsquo;t Choose WordPress I looked at WordPress first and while it could have done what I wanted, I decided I wanted something that I didn&amp;rsquo;t host so if my server goes down I can still access it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
